

Name: Prajakta Kedar

Contact No: 8208181424

**Current Location: Pune** 

**Email:** 

Prajaktakedar027@gmail.com

# **Professional Summary**

Smart and hardworking in any domain. Responsible Process Specialist, passionate about delivering outstanding quality and service.

Offering 7 + years of experience in the industry with a history of recognition for performance.

An energetic self-starter and team builder.

Connects with end user, Requisitioners, Buyer, Stakeholders and delivery partners to get the job done.

Navigate high-stress situation and achieves goals on time with quality.

To Work in Challenging environment, where I can apply my knowledge, acquire my skill and build a successful career by contributing to the organization growth.

**Work Experience** 

## **Infosys BPM Limited**

#### Designation in Account Payable(P2P) -Assistance Accountant October 2020-2023 till Date:

#### Job Profile:

- Working in Rio-Tinto process at Infosys as a working "Assistance accountant"
- To Calculate GST, QST.6Y,6D, PU, PT, PE etc., tax code
- To Process Correction General Entry in MIRO T-Code.
- To Process Direct Debit SAP via FV60 T-Code
- Processing intercompany invoice
- P2P cycle end to end
- To Process Arriba compliant PO, Arriba non-Compliant PO
- To Process PO based /non-PO based invoice
- To Process Row Material invoice
- To Process OTM invoice
- To Process FI and Non-FI invoice
- To Process Service and Material invoice
- Process invoice with ERS short Paid invoice
- Payment to vendor
- Duplicate PO analysis and rejection
- To Process multiple SES with multiple currency invoice
- Processing invoice debit and credit note and subsequent credit /debit and partially credit in SAP payment
- To processing 2-way match (passport) Invoice 3- way match invoice, create GL entry reversal AccM (Accounts maintenance)
- ERS invoice /credit paid/ not paid coding relies invoice various (Z, R, A, V,) types of block payment invoice
- Managed GR /IR entry's
- Managed SAP software T-Code transaction
- Follow-up daily Emails End user off site /client, on site holders
- Maintain Daily Production Tracker
- Follow-up daily Emails Vendors / buyers/suppliers (WMP document)

## **Infosys BPM Limited**

## Designation in Senior Process Executive April 2019 to September 2020:

#### Job Profile:

- Worked at Conagra brand Genpact pallet base processes as a "Senior Process" Executive
- Managed SAP R3TP Enterprises Transaction Code
- Managed Inventory management stock and warehouse management
- Managed turnkey warehouse various types of warehouses
- Maintain Daily Production Tracker
- Managed inventory IDOC and variance Report
- External or internal rejection
- Validate Report
- Managed GI, GR, PO create handling ware house entry, Monthly Reconciliation work etc.
- To create scraping entry in SAP system

## **Designation in Customer Support January 2017 to March 2019:**

#### Job Profile:

- Worked at Next Generation CDN Pvt. Ltd as a customer support (CS) in Next Generation
- Managed On side off side Customer enquires/errors/ complaints
- Taking daily Follow-up from supervisor's team
- Managed and updating work tracker daily
- Managed VMware Software for resolving complaints/errors

# Designation in Office Assistance March 2015 to October 2016:

#### Job Profile:

- Worked as "office Assistance" Saakshi Builders and Developers Pvt Ltd
- Managed all types of account, cash management bills (O to C)
- Experience in working with multiple vendors and geographically distributed teams

## **Key Skills and Technical Knowledge:**

Technical : Proficient in MS office MS Power Point and MS Excel, Knowledge of various

Application related to Work ERP, Citrix SAP, oracle, MIGO ME23N VMware Oracle,

## **Hobbies:**

- Listening music
- Drawing
- Cocking

# **Academic Qualification:**

• Master of Arts Yashavantaro Chauhan University, Nashik, Maharashtra, India

## **Certifications / Professional Awards:**

- Certified course completing with Inventory Management in Great Learning Academy
- Certified course completing with Financial Accounting in Great Learning Academy
- Certified course completing with Operation Management in Great Learning Academy
- Certified course completing with Amazon services
- Undergone business etiquette training (milestone 2.0 and 3.0)

- Certified in domain T100 and T200
- Certified in domain T105 Account fundamental
- BPM I Leap 2.0 and 3.0
- Being Awesome appraisal award from client
- SAP ERP
- Windows 7,8, and 10
- Accounting
- Organization skill
- Problem solving

# Languages known:

- English
- Marathi
- Hindi

I hereby declare that all the information provided in my resume is true to best of my knowledge.

Date / /

Your sincerely

(Prajakta V. Kedar)

